American Vaudeville Museum collection, 1850s-2007 (bulk 1910s-1940s)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IX: Sheet Music, 1859-1945 (bulk 1905-1935), 2 linear feet
  Sheet music can also be found in the Performers files and in individual or family collections, particularly the Dixon-Freeman collection.
  - Librettos (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Norma, composed by [Vincenzo] Bellini (Ditson & Co.'s standard opera libretto, 28 pp.) 1859
    Die Walküre, a musical drama in three acts, by Richard Wagner; English version by Charles Henry Meltzer; pub. by Fred. Rullman, Inc. (New York); libretto, for Metropolitan Opera House Grand Opera ca. 1920s
  - Sheet Music, A (Box 25, Folder 2)
    After All (Lee S. Roberts, lyric J. Will Callahan) 1919
    After the Ball (Charles K. Harris) 1920
    Ain't She Sweet? (Milton Ager, lyric Jack Yellen) 1927
    Album of Bert Williams Famous Song Hits 1905, 1932 - 2 copies
    All Alone Monday from The Ramblers (Harry Ruby, lyric Bert Kalmar) 1926
    All She Does Is Follow them Around (Maurice Abraham, lyric Grant Clarke) 1914
    All I Want Is You (Benny Davis, Sidney Clare, Harry Akst) 1927
    Alma (Jean Briquet, English lyric George V. Hobart - translated from Alma, Where Do You Live? Alma Wo Wohnst Du, German lyric Adolf Philipp) 1910
    Along the Rocky Road to Dublin (Bert Grant, lyric Joe Young) 1915
    Always Be Honey to Me (Jeff Branen, Arthur Lange, Max Prival) 1915
    Always in My Heart [Forever on My Mind] (J. Fred Coots, lyric Roy Turk) 1932
    Am I Blue? (Harry Akst, lyric Grant Clarke) from On with the Show 1929
    And Then (Herman Paley, lyric Alfred Bryan) 1913
    Are You Sorry? (Milton Ager, lyric Benny Davis) 1925
    Are You Lonesome To-night? (Roy Turk and Lou Handman) 1927
    Arizona Stars Song (Carl Rupp, lyric George Little) 1923
    At Sundown [When Love Is Calling Me Home] (Walter Donaldson) 1927
    At the End of the Broken Down Trail (Fred Rose) 1931
  - Sheet Music, B - D (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Back in the Old Sunday School (Phillips H. Lord, May Singhi Breen, Peter DeRose) 1932
    Back in Your Own Back Yard (Al Jolson, Billy Rose, Dave Dreyer) 1928
    Beside an Open Fireplace (Paul Denniker, Will Osborne) 1929
    Boogie Woogie on W.C. Handy's St. Louis Blues (Earl Hines) 1914, 1942, 1945
    Boston Town (Felix Rice, John Rehauser, lyric Wilbur Mack) 1907
    Breezin Along with the Breeze (Haven Gillespie, Seymour Simons, Richard A. Whiting) 1926
    By the River Sainte Marie (Harry Warren, lyric Edgar Leslie) 1931
    Call Me Darling, Call Me Sweetheart, Call Me Dear (Sag Mir Darling, English lyric Dorothy Dick) 1931 (German music and lyric Bert Reisfeld, Mart Fryberg, Rolf Marbot)
    Cheerful Little Earful from Sweet and Low (Harry Warren, lyric Ira Gershwin, Billy Rose) 1930
    Cross My Heart, Mother [I Love You] (Jack McCoy, Sam Williams, lyric Al Piantadosi) 1925
    Crying for You (Ned Miller, Chester Cohn) 1923
    Dinah (Harry Akst, lyric Sam M. Lewis, Joe Young) 1925
    Dreamy Melody (Ted Koehler, Frank Magine, C. Naset) 1922
    Drifting (Gertrude Lincoff, lyric Max Siegel) 1930
  - Sheet Music, E - F (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Eddie Cantor Song and Joke Book for 1934
    Feather Your Nest [Emplumez le Nid] (Kendis Brockman, Howard Johnson, French lyric A. Bollaert) 1920
    Five Salted Peanuts (Charlie Abbott) 1945
    Follow the Swallow (Ray Henderson, lyric Billy Rose, Mort Dixon) 1924
    Footlight Favorites (Frank Banta) 1897
    Forgetting (Ray Mitchell) 1927
    Forgive Me (Milton Ager, lyric Jack Yellen) 1927
    Forgive Me (Milton Ager, lyric Jack Yellen) 1927 (different cover)
    Francis & Day's Album of Harry Lauder's Popular Songs 1905
  - Sheet Music, G - H (Box 25, Folder 5)
    The Gaby Glide (Louis A. Hirsh, lyric Harry Pilcer) 1911
    Garden of My Dreams, from Ziegfeld Follies (Louis A. Hirsh, Dave Stamper, lyric Gene Buck) 1918
    The Gem Dance Folio for 1932 (Elliot Shapiro) 1932
    Gloomy Moon (Harry Geise) 1924
    Go As Far As You Like, Kid (W. Percival Kelgard, lyric Will H. Smith) 1909
    Good-night My Own Love (Jean Schwartz, lyric Stanislaus Stange and William Jerome), from The Musical Gems of F.C. Whitney's Piff! Paff! Pouf! A Musical Cocktail 1904
    Good Night Nurse (W. Raymond Walker, lyric Thomas J. Gray) 1912
    Gypsy Fiddles (Allie Wrubel) 1933
    Half a Moon [Is Better Than No Moon], from Honeymoon Lane (Herbert Reynolds, Eddie Dowling, James F. Hanley) 1926
    Hasta Manana [Until Tomorrow] (Al Hegbom, Egbert Van Alstyne, lyric Haven Gillespie) 1924
    Hello My Dearie, from Ziegfeld Follies (Dave Stamper, lyric Gene Buck) 1917
    Hello Evening Star (Jack Scholl, Henry Lodge, Emil Seidel) 1932
    Here I Am (Ray Henderson, lyric B.G. de Sylvia, Lew Brown) 1926
    Honolulu Eyes (Violinsky, lyric Howard Johnson) 1921
    The Hours I Spent with You (Little Jack Little, lyric Stan Lewis, Joe Young) 1927
    Hush-a-Bye (Robert E. Spencer, lyric Frank X. Galvin) 1926
  - Sheet Music, I (Box 25, Folder 6)
    I Can't Give You Anything But Love [Baby], from Lew Leslie's Blackbirds of 1928 (Jimmy McHugh, lyric Dorothy Fields) 1928 (lacks insert leaf, only has last page of the score)
    I Love a Lassie [Ma Scotch Bluebell] (Harry Lauder, Gerald Grafton) 1906
    I Love Me - I'm Wild About Myself (Will Mahoney) 1923
    I Love You - That's One Thing I Know (L. Wolfe Gilbert, Anatol Friedland) 1915
    I Miss a Little Miss [Who Misses Me in Sunny Tennessee] (J. Fred Coots, lyric Tot Seymour) 1930
    I Wonder Who's Dancing with You To-Night (Ray Henderson, lyric Mort Dixon, Billy Rose) 1924
    If I Could Be with You (Henry Creamer, Jimmy Johnson) 1926
    If My Love Could Talk (Harry Kogen, lyric Lou Holzer) 1935
    If You Had All the World and Its Gold (Albert Piantados, lyric Bartley Costello, Harry Edelheit) 1916
    I'll Keep On Loving You (Joseph B. Carey) 1916
    I'm a Lonesome Melody (George W. Meyer, lyric Joe Young) 1915
    I'm As Happy As Can Be (Hazel Graves, lyric Tell Taylor) 1926
    I'm Crazy 'Bout the Turkey Trot (George W. Meyer, lyric Joe Goodwin) 1911
    I'm Glad I Can Make You Cry (Charles R. McCarron, Carey Morgan) 1918
    I'm Looking Over a Four-Leaf Clover (Harry Woods, lyric Mort Dixon) 1927
    I'm Sorry That I Let That Gentleman In (Wilfred Herbert, lyric Jean Charez) 1902 (color photocopy)
    I'm Through [Shedding Tears Over You] (Edwin J. Weber, lyric Karyl Norman) 1922
    I'm Waiting in Dreamland for You (W.R. Williams) 1921
    In a Little Spanish Town (Mabel Wayne, lyric Lewis and Young) 1926
    In My Hide-Away (K. L. Binford) 1932
    In My Indiana Home (Larry Shay, lyric Harry Harris) 1929
    An Innocent Young Maid, from In Wall Street (Richard Carle, Maurice Levi, lyric Richard Carle) 1899
    It All Depends On You (B.G. De Sylva, Lew Brown, Ray Henderson) 1926
    It Had to Be You (Isham Jones, lyric Gus Kahn) 1924
    It's Never Too Late to Be Sorry (Jos. A. Burke, lyric James E. Dempsey) 1918
    I've Got Rings on My Fingers (Maurice Scott, lyric Weston and Barnes) 1909
    I've Got Everything I Want But You (Henry I. Marshall, lyric Marion Sunshine) 1913
  - Sheet Music, J - L (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Jigs and Reels, in two volumes, vol. I, academic edition undated
    Jimmy Valentine (Gus Edwards, lyric Edward Madden) 1910
    Just an Old Bouquet [of a Bye-Gone Day] (Lew Porter, Harry Edelbert, Mel Ball) 1928
    Just Cause I Lub Yo (Charles F. Gall, lyric Kate Thyson Mann) 1908 [color photocopy]
    Laugh! Clown! Laugh! (Ted Fiorito, lyric Lewis and Young) 1928
    Let Me Spend the Journey's End with You (Billy Baskette) 1926
    Let Us Waltz As We Say Goodbye (Art L. Beiner) 1925
    Limehouse Blues (Philip Braham, lyric Douglas Furber) 1922
    Little Brown Hut in the Hills (Ethwell "Eddie" Hanson) 1926
    Little Darling Marguerite (Eliza Doyle Smith) 1919
    Little Rag Baby Doll (Lewis F. Muir, lyric L. Wolfe Gilbert) 1913
    Log Cabin Lullaby (Cal De Voll) 1926
    London Bridge Is Falling Down on the Isle of Childhood Dreams (Harry I. Robinson, lyric Louis Robinson) 1923
    Lonesome [for You] (Earl Smith, Tell Taylor) 1925
    Long, Lean, Lanky Letty (Sydney Grant) 1914
    Looking at the World Thru Rose Colored Glasses (Tommy Malie and Jimmy Steiger) 1926
  - Sheet Music, M (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Madeira (Bert Kalmar, Harry Ruby, M. K. Jerome) 1925
    Make-Believe, from Show Boat (Jerome Kern, lyric Oscar Hammerstein) 1927
    Mammy's Little Coal Black Rose (Richard A. Whiting, lyric Raymond Egan) 1916
    Mammy's Lullaby (Pete Bontsema, Julius Peto, Marty Jacobi, lyric Al Cameron, Julius Seidor) 1929
    Marta, Rambling Rose of the Wildwood (Moises Simons, arr. Rosamond Johnson, English lyric L. Wolfe Gilbert [also in Spanish] 1931
    Martha: Just a Plain Old Fashioned Name (Joe L. Sanders) 1922
    Mem-o-ries (Harry H. Williams, lyric Morgan Brown) 1914
    Mickey (Neil Moret, lyric Harry Williams) 1918
    Mister Five by Five (Don Raye, Gene De Paul) 1942
    Mister Gallagher and Mister Shean, from Ziegfeld Follies 1922 (Ed Gallagher, Al Shean) 1922
    Moments with You (Nat Shilkret, lyric Jack Yellen) 1928
    Momsy (Jack Yellen, Ed "Nemo" Roth, Dave Ringle) 1927
    Moonbeam Kiss Her for Me (Harry Woods, lyric Mort Dixon) 1927
    Moonlight and Roses [Bring Mem'ries of You] (Edwin H. Lemare, Ben Black, Neil Moret) 1925
    My Isle of Golden Dreams (Walker Blaufuss, lyric Gus Kahn) 1919
    My Sin (B. G. De Sylva, Lew Brown, Ray Henderson) 1929
    My Song of the Nile (Al Bryan, George W. Meyer) 1929 (with 15 other songs; untitled compilation with star portraits)
    My Twilight Queen (Lou Hirsh, lyric Jean Havez) 1907
  - Sheet Music, O - R (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Oh By Jingo! Oh By Gee! You're the Only Girl for Me (Albert Von Tilzer, lyric Lew Brown) 1919
    Oh, Donna Clara (J. Petersburgski, lyric Beda; English version Irving Caesar) 1930
    Oh! Gee, Oh! Gosh, Oh! Golly I'm in Love, from Zeigfeld Follies (Ernest Brener, lyric Olson and Johnson) 1923
    Oh Johnny, Oh Johnny, Oh (Abe Olman, lyric Ed Rose) 1917 [Olman portrait on the cover]
    Oh Johnny, Oh Johnny, Oh (Abe Olman, lyric Ed Rose) 1917 [different edition, flapper on the cover]
    Only a Rose You Once Gave Me (H.C. Weasner) 1926
    Only a Weaver of Dreams (Ethwell Eddie Hanson) 1924
    Pal of My Cradle Days (Al Piantadosi, lyric Marshall Montgomery) 1925
    Peg O' My Heart (Fred Fischer, lyric Alfred Bryan) 1913
    Poor Butterfly, from The Big Show at the New York Hippodrome (Raymond Hubbell, lyric John L. Golden) 1916
    Put Away a Little Ray of Golden Sunshine for a Rainy Day (Fred E. Ahlert, lyric Sam M. Lewis and Joe Young) 1924
    Put Away a Little Ray of Golden Sunshine for a Rainy Day (Fred E. Ahlert, lyric Sam M. Lewis and Joe Young) 1924 (different edition)
    Put Your Arms Around Me, Honey [I Never Knew Any Girl Like You] (Albert Von Tilzer, lyric Junie McCree) 1910
    Rae! Rae! Rae! (John C. Rundback) music section, New York American and Journal July 8, 190[6] [color photocopy]
    Reaching for the Moon (Benny Davis, Jesse Greer) 1926
    Rememb'ring, from Topsy and Eva (Duncan Sisters) 1923
    River, Stay 'Way from My Door (Harry Woods, lyric Mort Dixon) 1931
    Roam On My Little Gypsy Sweetheart (Francis Wheeler, Irving Kahal, Ted Snyder) 1927
    Rocky Mountain Rose (M. K. Jerome, lyric Joan Jasmyn, Wm. Tracey) 1931
    Roll Along Prairie Moon (Ted Fierito, Harry MacPherson, Albert Von Tilzer) 1935
    A Rose and a Kiss, from La Paloma (Mabel Wayne, lyric Bennée Russell) 1931
    Rose of Washington Square (James F. Hanley, lyric Ballard Macdonald) 1920
  - Sheet Music, S (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Save Your Sorrow [for To-morrow] (Al Sherman, lyric B.G. De Sylva) 1925
    Shanghai Honeymoon (Wm. L. Shockley, Chas. J. Hausman, Lester Melrose) 1926
    Side by Side (Harold Dixon, lyric Claude Sacre) 1922
    Side by Side (Harry Woods) 1927
    A Smile Will Go a Long Long Way (Benny Davis, Harry Akst) 1923
    Soft Boiled Ballads: A Collection of Heart-wrecking Songs (H. W. Hanemann) 1931
    Some of These Days (Shelton Brooks) 1922
    Somebody's Sweetheart I Want to Be (Cobb and Edwards) 1905
    Someday Soon (Edna Fischer, lyric Rosetta and Vivian Duncan) 1929
    Someday Sweetheart (John C. Spikes, Benjamin Spikes) 1924
    Sorry and Blue (Bob Elbel, Don Elbel) 1925
    Swanee River Dreams (Wendell Words Hall, Carson J. Robison) 1924
    Sweet Southern Love (Howard Johnson, Irving Bibo, Joe Darcy) 1925
    Sweet Sue - Just You (Victor Young, lyric Will J. Harris) 1928
    Sweet Varsity Sue from Life Begins in College (Charles Tobias, Al Lewis, Murray Mencher) 1937
    Sweetheart I'm Sorry [That I Made You Cry] (Frank Westphal, lyric Charley Newman) 1928
  - Sheet Music, T - V (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Take Me to the Midnight Cake Walk Ball (Eddie Cox, Arthur Jackson, Maurice Abraham) 1915
    Talking to the Moon (Billy Baskette, George A. Little) 1926
    That's Some Love (George M. Cohan) 1908
    That's Why You Make Me Cry (Joe Verges, Henri Therrien, Irwin LeClere) 1923
    There's Something Nice About Everyone But There's Everything Nice About You (Pete Wendling, lyric Arthur Terker, Alfred Bryan) 1927
    This Is My Love Song (Joe Burke, lyric Al Dubin) 1931
    This Is the Life (Irving Berlin) 1914
    To Think I Thought So Much of You and You Thought So Little of Me (Jack Little, lyric Tommie Malie) 1924
    To-Night You Belong to Me (Lee David, lyric Billy Rose) 1926
    Trading Smiles (Don Ramsay) 1907
    'Twas Only an Irishman's Dream (Rennie Cormack, lyric John J. O'Brien, Al Dubin) 1916
    Under the Moon (Ev. E. Lyn, Francis Wheeler, Ted Snyder) 1927
    Underneath the Stars with You (Nick Lucas, lyric Sam H. Stept) 1927
    The Victor Dance Folio, no.3 1907
  - Sheet Music, W - Y (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Waitin' for the Evenin' Mail [Sittin' On the Inside, Lookin' at the Outside] (Billy Baskettee) 1923 (2 copies)
    Waitin' for the Moon (Sam Lerner, lyric Joe Brown) 1925
    What Can I Say After I Say I'm Sorry? (Walter Donaldson, Abe Lyman) 1926
    When I Was the Dandy and You Were the Belle (Lou Handman and Dave Dreyer, lyric Herman Ruby) 1924
    When I Wore My Daddy's Brown Derby [and You Wore Your Mother's Blue Gown] (Max Rich, lyric Harry Pease, Chas O'Flynn) 1931
    When It's Apple Blossom Time in Normandy (Mellor Gifford and Trevor) 1912
    When It's Lamp Lightin' Time in the Valley (Joe Lyons, Sam C. Hart, The Vagabonds (Harold - Dean - Curt) 1933
    When the Chapel Bells Were Ringing (Clarence Gaskill, lyric Cal De Voll) 1931
    When You Come to the End of the Day (Frank Westphal, lyric Gus Kahn) 1929
    When You're in Love (Walter Donaldson, Walter Blaufuss) 1926
    Where Did Robinson Crusoe Go with Friday on Saturday Night? (George W. Meyer, lyric Sam M. Lewis, Joe Young) 1916
    Where the Mill Stream Winds Its Way (Harold Dixon, lyric Claude Sacre) 1923
    Where the Song Birds Sing "Good Mornin' (Ed East, W.R. Williams) 1931
    Where the Shy Little Violets Grow (Gus Kahn, Harry Warren) 1928
    Wonderful One (Paul Whiteman, Ferdie Grofé, adapted from a theme by Marshall Nielan; lyric Dorothy Terriss) 1923
    Wait You Believe in Me (Lester Palmer, Jess Williams) 1926
    With My Eyes Wide Open I'm Dreaming (Mack Gordon, Harry Revel) 1934 (photocopy)
    Would You Take Me Back Again? (Peter De Rose, Alfred Solman) 1931
    You Can't Make a Fool Out of Me (Egbert Van Alstyne, lyric Paul Cunningham) 1923
    You'll Always Be the Same Sweet Baby (A. Seymour Brown) 1916
    You're Lucky to Me, from Lew Leslie's Blackbirds of 1930 (Eubie Blake, lyric Andy Razaf) 1930
    You're Tired of Me (Don York, Jack Sadler, Pauline Brown) 1931
- Series X: Periodicals, 1894-2007, 7.75 linear feet
  This series comprises primarily magazines, with some other items such as calendars and catalogues grouped here due to similar format. The titles are loosely grouped in pre-1950 and post-1950 sections, with titles represented by single or a few issues presented first and organized alphabetically by title. The groupings are based in part on size; the last two boxes are larger-format titles. Within each title, the issues are organized chronologically. There are also some tear sheets and an oversize article.
  Some periodicals can also be found in the Performers files.
  - Periodicals, pre-1950
    - Conkey's One-to-fill of 1920 (photocopy) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Conkey's One-to-fill of 1921 (photocopy) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Conkey's One-to-fill of 1923 (photocopy) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Liberty Nov 16, 1929 (lacks cover; half of p.33-34 cut out) (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - The Official Vaudeville Guide, v.3, no.2 (1927) (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Radio Stars Jan. 1931 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Theatre Arts Sep. 1940, Dec. 1940, Jan. 1951 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Periodicals, pre-1950
    - Loose tearsheets, reproductions ca. 1916-1960s (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - "The future of vaudeville" by Newman Levy; "The composer of 'Alexander's Ragtime Band'" by Irving Berlin, as told to Russel Crouse (first page only). Unidentified magazine ( 1911), pp. 75-80. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - The Billboard: the theatrical digest and show world review (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Oct. 13, 1928
    - The Billboard: the world's foremost amusement weekly
      Feb. 26, 1938 - cover Fred Allen
    - Broadway Weekly (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Sep. 21, 1904 - special vaudeville number
    - The Dance Magazine: glorifying the dance (Box 28, Folder 5)
      Nov. 1927 - cover Maryon Vadie
    - The Fra: a journal of affirmation (Box 28, Folder 6)
      v.5, no.3 ( June 1910) - the vaudeville number
    - Gallery of Players, from The Illustrated American (Box 28, Folder 7)
      no.2 ( 1894), ed. Charles Fdc. Nirdlinger
      no.3 ( 1894), ed. Marwell Hall
    - Paris Qui Chante (Box 28, Folder 8)
      , 4e année, no. 189 ( Sept. 2, 190-)
    - Pictures of Movie Stars, with stories by Mae Tinée (Racine: Whitman Pub. Co., 1937) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - The Player: The official organ of The White Rats of America, Inc. (Box 28, Folder 10)
      v.1, no.14 ( Mar. 11, 1910)
      v.2, no.34 ( July 29, 1910)
      v.4, no.33 ( July 21, 1911)
      Anniversary & Christmas number ( Dec. 22, 1911)
  - Periodicals, pre-1950
    - Stage: the magazine of after-dark entertainment (Box 29, Folder 1)
      Dec. 1936 - cover Fanny Brice
      Jan. 1938 - cover Ed Wynn
      Mar. 1938 - cover Beatrice Lillie
      Dec. 1940
    - The Theatre (pub. by Meyer Bros. & Co., New York) (Box 29, Folder 2)
      v.5, no.49 ( Mar. 1905) - cover Dustin Farnum as "The Virginian"
      v.5, no.52 ( June 1905) - cover Miss Eleanor Robson, in "She Stoops to Conquer"
    - Theatre Magazine: for the lovers of stage and screen ( Mar. 1927) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Variety Daily: News of the show world (published in Hollywood) (Box 29, Folder 4)
      v.33, no.38, sec. 2 ( Oct. 29, 1941)
    - New York Star (Box 29, Folder 5)
      v.15, no.26, whole no.390 ( Mar. 22, 1916)
      v.16, no.16, whole no.406 ( July 12, 1916)
    - The Vaudeville News
      v.9, no.25 ( Dec. 26, 1924)
    - The Vaudeville News and New York Star
      v.18, no.16 ( Oct. 13, 1928)
      v.19, no.4 ( Jan. 19, 1929)
      v.19, no.6 ( Feb. 2, 1929)
      v.19, no.22 ( May 25, 1929)
    - Wirth and Hamid, Fair Booking Inc. - world's greatest attractions ca. 1932 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Periodicals, pre-1950
    - The Illustrated London News (Box 30)
      Oct. 26, 1901
      Apr 11, 1903 (lacks front cover)
      Apr. 16, 1904
      Oct. 1, 1904; Oct. 8, 1904; Oct. 22, 1904
    - The New York Dramatic Mirror, Note: not available for viewing - extremely fragile, and most issues are partial rather than complete.
      May 1890 (pp. 7-10 only)
      Jan. 8, 1898; Jan. 15, 1898; Jan. 22, 1898; Jan. 29, 1898
      Feb. 5, 1898; Feb. 12, 1898; Feb. 19, 1898; Feb. 26, 1898
      Mar. 5, 1898; Mar. 12, 1898; Mar. 19, 1898; Mar. 26, 1898
      Apr. 2, 1898; Apr. 9, 1898; Apr. 16, 1898
      June 18, 1898
      July 16, 1898; July 23, 1898 July 30, 1898
      Nov. 15, 1902; Nov. 22, 1902 (1 sheet from each only)
    - Variety (published in New York)
      v.10, no.3 ( Mar. 28, 1908)
      v.10, no.4 ( Apr. 4, 1908)
      v.10, no.8 ( May 2, 1908)
      v.10, no.13 ( June 6, 1908)
      v.11, no.1 ( June 8, 1908)
      v.11, no.3 ( June 27, 1908)
      v.14, no.7 ( Apr. 24, 1909)
      v.15, no.7 ( July 24, 1909)
      v.15, no.8 ( July 31, 1909)
      v.18, no.13 ( June 4, 1910)
      v.19, no.2 ( June 18, 1910)
      v.23, no.4 ( July 1, 1911)
      v.23, no.12 ( Aug. 26, 1911)
    - Variety (published in New York)
      v.49, no.7 ( Jan. 11, 1918)
      v.50, no.7 ( Apr. 12, 1918)
  - Periodicals, post-1950
    - Loose article: "Fabulous Fanny" [ Fanny Brice], by Norman Katkov. Ladies' Home Journal ( Jan. 1953), pp. 48-49,123-129. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Loose article: "Refugee from Burlesque" [ Phil Silvers], by Stanley Frank. The Saturday Evening Post ( Jan. 1953), pp. 40-41,146-150. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Bloody Beautiful (Box 31, Folder 3)
      issue 1 ( 2000) - includes 7-inch red vinyl album of songs from 1916, performed in 1967/1972 by Ian Whitcomb
      issue 2 ( 2001?)- includes 10-inch blue vinyl marbleized album of songs by Al Bowlly, Lilian Harvey & Willie Firtsch, Sophie Tucker, and Durium Dance Band/ Fred Douglas (1928-36)
    - Life (Box 31, Folder 4)
      Oct. 23, 1950 - cover "TV gets top comics - Ed Wynn"
      Mar. 18, 1957 - cover " Beatrice Lillie, girls from New Ziegfeld Follies"
      Apr. 18, 1969 - cover " Mae West going strong at 75"
    - Life (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Feb. 19, 1971 - cover "Everybody's just wild about nostalgia"
      Dec. 31, 1971 - cover "The year in pictures 1971"
      Feb. 1980 - cover "Whatever became of Mary Astor and other lost stars?"
    - Look (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Apr. 10, 1951- cover "TV's old-new stars prove that laughs begin at 40"
    - Paris Match (Box 31, Folder 7)
      Jan. 15, 1972- cover "Chevalier: 30 pages"
  - Periodicals, post-1950
    - Bijou (Box 32, Folder 1)
      Apr. 1977
    - The Call Boy: The official journal of the British Music Hall Society (Box 32, Folder 2)
      v.34, no.1 ( spring 1997)
      v.36, no.1 ( winter 1999) - v.39, no.4 ( winter 2003)
    - The Call Boy: The official journal of the British Music Hall Society (Box 32, Folder 3)
      v.40, no.1 ( spring 2003) - v.44, no.1 ( spring 2007)
    - Dance Magazine (Box 32, Folder 4)
      Sep. 1966
    - Juggle: the official magazine of the International Jugglers' Association (Box 32, Folder 5)
      July/Aug. 2000
      Mar./Apr. 2001
      Nov./Dec. 2006 (complete and partial copies)
      and related correspondence to Frank Cullen
    - The Keaton Chronicle (Box 32, Folder 6)
      v.3, issue 2 ( spring 1995)
      v.4, issue 2 ( spring 1995), issue 3 ( summer 1996), issue 4 ( autumn 1996)
      v.5, issue 1 ( spring 1995), issue 2 ( spring 1997), issue 3 ( summer 1997)
      v.6, issue 1 ( spring 1995), issue 2 ( spring 1998), issue 4 ( autumn 1998)
      v.7, issue 1 ( winter 1999), issue 2 ( spring 1999), issue 3 ( summer 1999)
      v.7, issue 4/v.8, issue 1 ( autumn 1999/winter 2000)
      v.8, issue 2 ( spring 2000)
    - Liberty: the nostalgia magazine (Box 32, Folder 7)
      v.1, no.4 ( spring 1972), no.7 ( winter 1972)
    - Lompoc Picayune-Intelligencer: the official newsletter of the W.C. Fields Fan Club (Box 32, Folder 8)
      issue no.8 ( spring 1996)
      issue no.9 ( summer 1996)
      issue no.10 ( fall 1996/winter 1997)
      issue no.11 ( spring 1997)
      issue no.12 ( winter 1998)
      issue no.15 ( winter 2000)
      issue no.16 ( winter/spring 2001)
    - Mad (Box 32, Folder 9)
      no.430 ( June 2003) - special edition: Boston Comedy & Movie Festival
    - Marquee: the journal of the Theatre Historical Society (Box 32, Folder 10)